olr.com 2017-07-03

# Privacy Policy

On-Line Residential, Inc. (“OLR”), and its affiliate companies are committed to protecting your privacy. By using the website, OLR.com (“Website”), you signify your acceptance of our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy please discontinue with your use of the web site. Should we change our Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on our Website so that you, as the user, will always be aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Please refer back to this policy each time that you use the Website. 

The Collection of Information  
You can visit the Website without disclosing any personal information. However, should you register on the Website, you will be asked for information that identifies you, including your name and email address. This information allows us to give you access to advance features of the Website. OLR does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. OLR does, however, collect and track aggregate statistics about our users on a non-personally identifiable basis so that we can monitor and improve our services. 

Collection of IP Addresses  
When you visit an Internet Site, your computer’s unique address, called an IP address, is recorded by the company’s web servers. These addresses are archived by us. We do not release this information to any third parties. 

Internet Cookies  
Internet Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer’s hard drive by your Internet browser. Cookies allow individual web sites the ability to recognize repeat visitors so that the site will identify your browser each time you interact with the particular web site. By themselves, Cookies cannot be used to find out the identity of an individual visitor. 

Links  
Please keep in mind that you may receive Cookies from third parties to which you link from our Website. We do not control these third-party Cookies and they are not subject to our Privacy Policy. You should contact these third-party web sites directly should you have any questions regarding their collection of information or their own privacy policy. 

If you have any further questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please Contact Us
